So if we look at what the AI
has been able to do for us, it's
been able to generate 15 videos.
We have 15 videos that the AI generated
at the end of the day.
So what we need to do is upload
these 15 videos.
And for you to do that, of course
you need a cloud to upload the video.
So on Instinctor platform, we have the media
segment.
The media segment just works like your Google
Drive.
So all you need to do is either
you drag the file into here, or you
just click to target the output, the out
where you have your videos, and you upload
all of them.
In order not to take so much time,
I have uploaded all the videos.
So what we need to do right now
is to let the AI know that we
have uploaded the video.